<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.thecollagen.co/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.thecollagen.co/collections/collagen-for-pescatarians.atom"/>
  <title>The Collagen Co.</title>
  <updated>2023-11-20T18:12:43+11:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>The Collagen Co.</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/products/7448821104798</id>
    <published>2023-11-20T18:12:43+11:00</published>
    <updated>2023-11-20T18:12:43+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.thecollagen.co/products/unflavoured-beauty-marine-collagen-powder-284g"/>
    <title>Unflavoured Beauty Marine Collagen Powder - 284g</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>The Collagen Co.</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0423/1492/4190/products/unflavoured-beauty-marine-collagen-powder-284g-808112.jpg?v=1700494126"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>The Collagen Co.<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            79.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h2>Description</h2>
<p><i>Marine collagen peptides, but not the ones you know. Because we make ours from fish scales — these contain the most collagen content among fish parts without that undesirable fishy smell and taste. And it's not just any fish scales. But instead, wild-caught ones off Australia's pristine coastal waters. Your skin, hair, nails, joints, and gut are in for a treat.</i></p>
<p>Beyond its versatility, the Unflavoured Beauty Marine Collagen Powder boasts exceptional efficacy. This is attributed to its carefully calibrated blend featuring abundant doses of Hydrolysed Marine Collagen Powder, Vitamin C, Hyaluronic Acid, and Niacinamide.</p>
<p>This powerful combination is dedicated to enhancing the radiance of your hair, skin, nails, joints, and gut. With this potent blend at work, premature ageing can be effectively prevented.</p>
<h2>Benefits</h2>
<p><i>Not</i> your typical 3-gram-per-serving marine collagen powder. Fueled by 10 grams of 100% pure Marine Collagen Peptides per serving, Beauty Marine Collagen is on a mission to illuminate, plump, hydrate, and restore; all in one. As with all our products, our marine collagen peptides are thoughtfully broken down until they're digestion-bypassing-tiny (a molecular size of less than 2 kDa on average).</p>
<p><span>Finally: they’re packed with Vitamin C, Hyaluronic Acid, and Niacinamide:</span></p>
<ul>
<li><span>Vitamin C shields your skin from free radicals</span></li>
<li><span>Hyaluronic Acid binds water for a firm complexion and well-lubricated joints</span></li>
<li><span>Niacinamide helps to maintain skin moisture and strengthen the skin barrier. </span></li>
</ul>
<p>So, why settle for the rest when you can have the best?</p>
<h2>Ingredients</h2>
<ul>
<li><strong>100% Pure Marine Collagen Peptides</strong></li>
</ul>
<p>10,000mg of Hydrolysed Marine Collagen Peptides created from sustainably sourced, wild caught fish scales from the coastal waters of Australia. With an average molecular weight of less than 2kDa, our PUREACOL MARINE™ Collagen Peptides are designed for optimum absorption and bioavailability.</p>
<ul>
<li><b>Ascorbic Acid (Vitamin C)<br></b></li>
</ul>
<p>Essential for collagen biosynthesis and the formation of collagen fibres. Vitamin C is also a powerful antioxidant that boosts the immune system and helps the body absorb iron. </p>
<ul>
<li><b>Sodium Hyaluronate (Hyaluronic Acid)<br></b></li>
</ul>
<p>A polysaccharide that occurs naturally in your skin. Hyaluronic Acid acts like a tiny sponge that pulls in water to quench and plump skin–giving it that dewy, glowy effect. It also keeps the joints lubricated and helps preserve bone strength.</p>
<ul>
<li><b>Vitamin B3 (Niacinamide)<br></b></li>
</ul>
<p>Aids in retaining skin moisture, fortifying the skin barrier, and reducing inflammation of the skin, commonly caused by skin conditions such as eczema and rosacea.</p>
<h2>Nutrition Information</h2>
<div><img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0423/1492/4190/files/UnflavouredBeautyMarineCollagenPowder-284g_1024x1024.png?v=1700440319" width="450" height="617"></div>
<h2>How to Use</h2>
<p><strong>How to enjoy it?<br></strong>Add 1 serving (2 scoops) to coffee, tea, oats or your favourite smoothie on the daily. Adding the powder first helps the collagen powder to mix in better. Can also be baked into cakes or biscuits for a delicious collagen snack.</p>
<p><img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0423/1492/4190/files/Meal_Plan_67.png?v=1718348314"></p>
<p><b><strong>How many serves a day?</strong><br></b>How much collagen you should take each day depends on your own health goals. Between 10-30grams of collagen peptides a day will give you visible results.<br><br>One serve a day is ideal if you want to combat fine lines and wrinkles, improve your hair and nail strength, ease joint pain, build muscle, improve gut health and get an overall energy boost.<br><br>Two serves a day will fast track your results. Have one serve morning and evening.<b><br><br><strong>Storage:</strong> </b>Store in a cool, dark place out of direct sunlight.</p>
<h2>Common FAQs</h2>
<h3><strong>Is collagen safe for pregnant and nursing mothers?</strong></h3>
<p>Yes, our collagen is perfectly safe for both pregnant and nursing mothers. In fact, there are many benefits of taking collagen whilst pregnant. Many of our customers have already experienced the benefits with skin elasticity, minimising the appearance of stretch marks and getting a radiant glow. Additionally, it promotes strong and healthy hair, already helping our customers to combat postpartum hair loss. <br><br>For any specific concerns, we recommend consulting with your general practitioner, who can provide personalised advice tailored to your needs.</p>
<h3><strong>How many serves per pack?</strong></h3>
<p>Experience the glow with our Beauty Marine Collagen, featuring 28 serves, allowing you to radiate with beauty. Each serve packs a remarkable 10,000mg of pure Australian marine collagen, Vitamin C, Hyaluronic Acid, and Niacinamide, ensuring you receive a generous dose of its nourishing benefits with every serving. </p>
<h3><strong>What’s the difference between Beauty Marine Collagen and Premium Collagen Peptides?</strong></h3>
<p>If you're contemplating which option suits you best, the decision ultimately boils down to your dietary preferences. Premium Collagen Peptides harness the power of hydrolyzed bovine collagen, stimulating the production of type 1, 2, and 3 collagens in the body. On the other hand, Beauty Marine Collagen utilises Pure Australian marine collagen, which contains type 1 collagen. <br><br>Rest assured, both options deliver radiant skin, lustrous hair, strong nails, and provide support for joint and gut health.</p>
<p><b> </b></p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>BMC</s:tag>
    <s:tag>GUT</s:tag>
    <s:tag>HAIR</s:tag>
    <s:tag>how-to-marine</s:tag>
    <s:tag>icons-unflv</s:tag>
    <s:tag>JOINTS</s:tag>
    <s:tag>label:NEW Formula</s:tag>
    <s:tag>menopause</s:tag>
    <s:tag>NAILS</s:tag>
    <s:tag>OVERALL</s:tag>
    <s:tag>PESC</s:tag>
    <s:tag>Powder</s:tag>
    <s:tag>sachet</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SKIN</s:tag>
    <s:tag>tiered</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/products/7448821104798</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="AUD">79.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>BMC-UNFLV28LP</s:sku>
      <s:grams>390</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
