<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/collections/all.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.thecollagen.co/collections/all"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.thecollagen.co/collections/super-beauty-greens.atom"/>
  <title>The Collagen Co.</title>
  <updated>2024-11-26T05:37:40+11:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>The Collagen Co.</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/products/8111855239326</id>
    <published>2024-11-26T05:37:40+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-11-26T05:37:40+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.thecollagen.co/products/tropical-punch-super-beauty-greens-308g"/>
    <title>Tropical Punch Super Beauty Greens - 308g</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>The Collagen Co.</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0423/1492/4190/files/tropical-punch-super-beauty-greens-308g-523385.png?v=1732650972"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>The Collagen Co.<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            65.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h2>Description</h2>
<p class="p1">Tropical Punch Super Beauty Greens takes the fuss (and chewing) out of wellness. </p>
<p class="p1">It's a fully loaded daily greens powder designed to give your body what it needs to neutralise toxins, support a strong immune system, optimally absorb nutrients, and refresh tired-looking skin, hair, and nails. </p>
<p class="p1">A single serving of Tropical Punch Super Beauty Greens delivers:</p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5,000mg Hydrolysed Collagen Peptides (Bovine)</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5 potent toxins-flushing Organic Greens</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>17 antioxidants-rich Superfoods</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>Natural Sea Mineral Complex to help fill gaps in your diet</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>6 fatigue-fighting Herbal Extracts</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>4 good-gut-bacteria-fuelling Prebiotics (5.6 billion CFUs)</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5 digestion-supporting Probiotics</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5 absorption-enhancing Digestive Enzymes</li>
</ul>
<p class="p1">No artificial flavours. Or sweeteners. Tropical Punch Super Beauty Greens brings you all the good stuff without the nasties in every delish, blood-sugar-friendly scoop.</p>
<h2>Benefits</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Your wellness drawer is about to get a lot neater. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Tropical Punch Super Beauty Greens combines the power of multiple health-beneficial supplements, such as your greens powder, multivitamins, and pre and probiotics. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Blending 5 Organic Greens, 17 nutrient-dense Superfoods, and Natural Mineral Sea Complex, it helps you cover the nutritional bases your body needs for optimal toxins neutralisation and immune function. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Another powerhouse ingredient is Hydrolysed Collagen Peptides. These bioactive peptides work to unlock a radiant, firm complexion, rejuvenate nails, and promote stronger, bouncier hair. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Made to encourage a balanced gut microbiome, Tropical Punch Super Beauty Greens brings together Pre and Probiotics and Digestive Enzymes — aiding digestion and supporting the relief of occasional discomforts, such as mild bloating, gas, and diarrhoea. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Get a smooth boost of natural, sustained energy from 6 Herbal Extracts designed to help you live life to the fullest.</span></p>
<h2>Ingredients</h2>
<ul></ul>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Organic Greens Blend (Spirulina, Chlorella, Alfalfa Grass, Wheat Grass, Barley Grass)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>- Spirulina is a blue-green microalgae rich in protein, B vitamins, and antioxidants like phycocyanins.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Chlorella is a green algae that contains chlorophyll, which aids detoxification. It's also high in antioxidant compounds, such as carotenoids, like lutein, beta-carotene, and zeaxanthin.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Alfalfa Grass has a long history of use as a medicinal herb for humans. It's a good source of calcium, potassium, phosphorus, iron, and vitamins A, C, E, and K.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Wheat Grass is a great source of cleansing chlorophyll, vitamins and minerals (vitamins A, B, C, and E, iron, calcium, and magnesium), antioxidant compounds, and bioflavonoids, such as apigenin.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Barley Grass is rich in vitamins C, B, and minerals like calcium, iron, and magnesium.<br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<b>100% Hydrolysed Collagen Peptides (Bovine</b>)<br><span class="s1"></span>Hydrolysed bioactive collagen from grass-fed, pasture-raised bovine. A tailored blend that stimulates type 1, type 2, and type 3 collagen. Combined, these promote healthy hair, skin, and nails, improve joint function, and support gut health.<br><br>
</li>
<li class="li2">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Super Fruit Juice Blend (Blackcurrant, Raspberry, Strawberry, Pomegranate, Blueberry, Cranberry, Elderberry, Acai, Goji)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>These 5 super fruits offer a high concentration of vitamins, minerals, fibre, and antioxidants. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>Of particular importance for beauty and overall health is vitamin C, which may help protect against oxidative stress by scavenging destructive free radicals and stimulating the body's natural production of collagen, plus hyaluronic acid. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Organic Fruit and Vegetable Blend (Beetroot, Carrot, Kale, Spinach, Acai, Grape, Apple, Broccoli Sprout)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>Eight incredibly nutrient-dense fruits and vegetables with high amounts of essential vitamins, minerals, antioxidants, and fibre that you may be missing out on your daily diet. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>An unfamiliar ingredient that might have caught your eye is Broccoli Sprout — this refers to a 3-5 day-old broccoli seed sprout that offers more nutrition benefits than the mature plant, including increased concentrations of powerful antioxidants like vitamin C and a phytochemical called sulforaphane. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Natural Sea Mineral Complex<br></b><span class="s1"></span>Derived from red marine algae. A rich source of bioavailable calcium and 72 trace minerals, including magnesium, iron, and selenium, Natural Sea Mineral Complex offers a fuss-free way to fill the nutrition gaps in your diet. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Prebiotics (Partially Hydrolysed Guar Gum, Chicory Root Fibre, Acacia Fibre, Organic Green Banana Resistant Starch Powder)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>These 4 prebiotic fibres aren't digestible by your body, so they travel down to your lower digestive tract relatively intact and become a crucial food source for your gut's friendly microorganisms. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>This encourages a balanced gut microbiome, which promotes an optimal environment for your digestive system and overall health.<br><br>
</li>
<li class="li2">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Probiotics Blend (<i>Lactobacillus acidophilus, Lactobacillus plantarum, Lactobacillus rhamnosus, Bifidobacterium lactis, Bifidobacterium longum</i>)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>If prebiotics are "fertilisers" for beneficial gut microbes, probiotics are the "seeds" that'll populate your digestive tract and improve the composition of your gut microbiome. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>Different strains of probiotics perform different biological actions in the gut; the 5 probiotic strains in Super Beauty Greens were specifically selected for their unique and synergistic benefits in supporting overall health, vitality, gut, and immune support. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Digestive Enzyme Blend (Protease, Amylase, Lipase, Cellulase, Lactase)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>A comprehensive blend of 5 digestive enzymes that support good digestion — promoting optimal nutrient absorption while minimising the occasional gas and bloating. <br><span class="s1"></span>- Protease enzymes break down proteins into smaller peptides and amino acids for absorption. <br>- Amylase enzymes break down carbohydrates into simpler sugars like glucose for absorption.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Lipase enzymes break down dietary fats into fatty acids and glycerol for absorption.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Cellulase enzymes break down cellulose, a plant fibre humans can't digest without assistance.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Lactase enzymes break down lactose, the sugar found in dairy products. <br><br><b></b>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<b>Herbal Extract Blend (L-theanine, Panax Ginseng, Cacao Bean Polyphenols, Milk Thistle, Gotu Kola)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>A blend of natural, energising actives that'll have you maintaining peak performance from day to night. Get ready to live your best life.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Nutritional Information</h2>
<p><img height="889" width="500" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0423/1492/4190/files/SBG_-_Tropical_Punch_-_NIPS.png?v=1732526921" alt=""></p>
<h2>How to Use</h2>
<p>Fill your glass or bottle with 250-350ml of cold or hot water.</p>
<p>Add 1 serving (2 heaped scoops) to the water, and blend well.<b></b></p>
<p>One serving a day is recommended for the best results.<b></b></p>
<p>Store in a cool, dark place out of direct sunlight.</p>
<h2>Common FAQs</h2>
<h3><strong>Can Super Beauty Greens be taken alongside Glow shakes, Premium Collagen Peptides and/or Collagen Dream?</strong></h3>
<p>Absolutely, you can take Super Beauty Greens with Glow shakes and/or Premium Collagen Peptides! All of our collagen products are designed to complement each other.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Super Beauty Greens: Boost your fruit and veggie game effortlessly, packed with collagen, Prebiotics, Probiotics, and Digestive Enzymes to keep you light, energised, and bloat-free.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Glow Shakes: These shakes are designed to help with weight management, skin health, and overall wellness with 29 grams of protein and collagen peptides.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Premium Collagen Peptides: Added skin loving ingredients like hyaluronic acid and supports skin elasticity, hair, nails, and joints.</p>
</li>
<li>Collagen Dream: Collagen-infused hot chocolate that guides you into a peaceful slumber, and awakens you with revitalised beauty.</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Is collagen safe for pregnant and nursing mothers?</strong></h3>
<p>Yes, our collagen is perfectly safe for both pregnant and nursing mothers. In fact, there are many benefits of taking collagen whilst pregnant. Many of our customers have already experienced the benefits with skin elasticity, minimising the appearance of stretch marks and getting a radiant glow. Additionally, it promotes strong and healthy hair, already helping our customers to combat postpartum hair loss.<br><br>For any specific concerns, we recommend consulting with your general practitioner, who can provide personalised advice tailored to your needs.</p>
<h3><strong>Can I take all the products together? Is there a limit?</strong></h3>
<p>There’s no official limit on collagen intake, so you can enjoy it your way! Our collagen products are made to complement each other, giving you the ultimate glow. If you’re just starting your collagen journey, you may want to start with 1 serving a day and gradually increase as you feel. It’s all about finding your glow-getting groove!</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>GUT</s:tag>
    <s:tag>how-to-greens</s:tag>
    <s:tag>icons-greens</s:tag>
    <s:tag>IMMUNITY</s:tag>
    <s:tag>OVERALL</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SKIN</s:tag>
    <s:tag>tiered</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/products/8111855239326</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="AUD">65.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SBG-TP28LP</s:sku>
      <s:grams>420</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/products/8111857205406</id>
    <published>2024-11-26T05:36:50+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-11-26T05:36:50+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.thecollagen.co/products/apple-blackcurrant-super-beauty-greens-308g"/>
    <title>Apple Blackcurrant Super Beauty Greens - 308g</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>The Collagen Co.</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0423/1492/4190/files/apple-blackcurrant-super-beauty-greens-308g-990237.png?v=1732650972"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>The Collagen Co.<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            65.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h2>Description</h2>
<p class="p1">Eat the rainbow with ease — no farmer's market trip required. </p>
<p class="p1">Powered by an Organic Greens Blend (consisting of 5 essential leafy greens) and Superfoods complex (17 fruits and vegetables), Apple Blackcurrant Super Beauty Greens is a convenient and tasty way to meet your body's whole food nutrition needs for detox and immune support. </p>
<p class="p1">And if all that doesn't sound impressive enough, every serving also stars:</p>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5,000mg Hydrolysed Collagen Peptides (Bovine)</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>Natural Sea Mineral Complex</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>6 stimulating, crash-proof Herbal Extracts</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>4 gut-loving Prebiotics</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5 friendly bacteria boosting Probiotics (5.6 billion CFUs)</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5 digestion-easing Digestive Enzymes</li>
</ul>
<p class="p1">Apple Blackcurrant Super Beauty Greens keeps things real with a natural low-calorie sweetener with zero impact on blood sugar levels and no artificial flavours.</p>
<h2>Benefits</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><span>A greens powder that's so much more than greens. Of course, there are greens: 5 potent cleansing Organic Greens, to be exact. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>But they're also paired with Superfoods and a Natural Mineral Sea Complex to feed your body with a cocktail of sometimes hard-to-get nutrients for<strong> immune and overall well-being support. </strong></span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Bioactive Hydrolysed Collagen Peptides <strong>enhance skin's radiance</strong> and improve its overall appearance, nourish and <strong>strengthen nails</strong>, and boost <strong>hair's thickness</strong> and volume. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>The 3-in-1 symbiotic mix of Pre and Probiotics and Digestive Enzymes helps <strong>balance bacteria in the gut</strong> and allow optimal nutrient absorption — fortifying your digestive health. The result is sweet, sweet relief from occasional digestive upsets, such as bloating, gas, and discomfort. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Lastly, kick your day up a notch with 6 natural, energising Herbal Extracts that'll help you knock off everything on your to-do list.</span></p>
<h2>Ingredients</h2>
<ul></ul>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Organic Greens Blend (Spirulina, Chlorella, Alfalfa Grass, Wheat Grass, Barley Grass)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>- Spirulina is a blue-green microalgae rich in protein, B vitamins, and antioxidants like phycocyanins.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Chlorella is a green algae that contains chlorophyll, which aids detoxification. It's also high in antioxidant compounds, such as carotenoids, like lutein, beta-carotene, and zeaxanthin.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Alfalfa Grass has a long history of use as a medicinal herb for humans. It's a good source of calcium, potassium, phosphorus, iron, and vitamins A, C, E, and K.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Wheat Grass is a great source of cleansing chlorophyll, vitamins and minerals (vitamins A, B, C, and E, iron, calcium, and magnesium), antioxidant compounds, and bioflavonoids, such as apigenin.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Barley Grass is rich in vitamins C, B, and minerals like calcium, iron, and magnesium.<br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<b>100% Hydrolysed Collagen Peptides (Bovine</b>)<br><span class="s1"></span>Hydrolysed bioactive collagen from grass-fed, pasture-raised bovine. A tailored blend that stimulates type 1, type 2, and type 3 collagen. Combined, these promote healthy hair, skin, and nails, improve joint function, and support gut health.<br><br>
</li>
<li class="li2">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Super Fruit Juice Blend (Blackcurrant, Raspberry, Strawberry, Pomegranate, Blueberry, Cranberry, Elderberry, Acai, Goji)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>These 5 super fruits offer a high concentration of vitamins, minerals, fibre, and antioxidants. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>Of particular importance for beauty and overall health is vitamin C, which may help protect against oxidative stress by scavenging destructive free radicals and stimulating the body's natural production of collagen, plus hyaluronic acid. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Organic Fruit and Vegetable Blend (Beetroot, Carrot, Kale, Spinach, Acai, Grape, Apple, Broccoli Sprout)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>Eight incredibly nutrient-dense fruits and vegetables with high amounts of essential vitamins, minerals, antioxidants, and fibre that you may be missing out on your daily diet. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>An unfamiliar ingredient that might have caught your eye is Broccoli Sprout — this refers to a 3-5 day-old broccoli seed sprout that offers more nutrition benefits than the mature plant, including increased concentrations of powerful antioxidants like vitamin C and a phytochemical called sulforaphane. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Natural Sea Mineral Complex<br></b><span class="s1"></span>Derived from red marine algae. A rich source of bioavailable calcium and 72 trace minerals, including magnesium, iron, and selenium, Natural Sea Mineral Complex offers a fuss-free way to fill the nutrition gaps in your diet. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Prebiotics (Partially Hydrolysed Guar Gum, Chicory Root Fibre, Acacia Fibre, Organic Green Banana Resistant Starch Powder)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>These 4 prebiotic fibres aren't digestible by your body, so they travel down to your lower digestive tract relatively intact and become a crucial food source for your gut's friendly microorganisms. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>This encourages a balanced gut microbiome, which promotes an optimal environment for your digestive system and overall health.<br><br>
</li>
<li class="li2">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Probiotics Blend (<i>Lactobacillus acidophilus, Lactobacillus plantarum, Lactobacillus rhamnosus, Bifidobacterium lactis, Bifidobacterium longum</i>)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>If prebiotics are "fertilisers" for beneficial gut microbes, probiotics are the "seeds" that'll populate your digestive tract and improve the composition of your gut microbiome. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>Different strains of probiotics perform different biological actions in the gut; the 5 probiotic strains in Super Beauty Greens were specifically selected for their unique and synergistic benefits in supporting overall health, vitality, gut, and immune support. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Digestive Enzyme Blend (Protease, Amylase, Lipase, Cellulase, Lactase)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>A comprehensive blend of 5 digestive enzymes that support good digestion — promoting optimal nutrient absorption while minimising the occasional gas and bloating. <br><span class="s1"></span>- Protease enzymes break down proteins into smaller peptides and amino acids for absorption. <br>- Amylase enzymes break down carbohydrates into simpler sugars like glucose for absorption.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Lipase enzymes break down dietary fats into fatty acids and glycerol for absorption.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Cellulase enzymes break down cellulose, a plant fibre humans can't digest without assistance.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Lactase enzymes break down lactose, the sugar found in dairy products. <br><br><b></b>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<b>Herbal Extract Blend (L-theanine, Panax Ginseng, Cacao Bean Polyphenols, Milk Thistle, Gotu Kola)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>A blend of natural, energising actives that'll have you maintaining peak performance from day to night. Get ready to live your best life.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Nutritional Information</h2>
<p><img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0423/1492/4190/files/SBG_-_Apple_Blackcurrant_-_NIPS.png?v=1732526750" width="500" height="889"></p>
<h2>How to Use</h2>
<p><meta charset="utf-8">Fill your glass or bottle with 250-350ml of cold or hot water.</p>
<p>Add 1 serving (2 heaped scoops) to the water, and blend well.<b></b></p>
<p>One serving a day is recommended for the best results.<b></b></p>
<p>Store in a cool, dark place out of direct sunlight.</p>
<h2>Common FAQs</h2>
<h3><strong>Can Super Beauty Greens be taken alongside Glow shakes, Premium Collagen Peptides and/or Collagen Dream?</strong></h3>
<p>Absolutely, you can take Super Beauty Greens with Glow shakes and/or Premium Collagen Peptides! All of our collagen products are designed to complement each other.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Super Beauty Greens: Boost your fruit and veggie game effortlessly, packed with collagen, Prebiotics, Probiotics, and Digestive Enzymes to keep you light, energised, and bloat-free.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Glow Shakes: These shakes are designed to help with weight management, skin health, and overall wellness with 29 grams of protein and collagen peptides.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Premium Collagen Peptides: Added skin loving ingredients like hyaluronic acid and supports skin elasticity, hair, nails, and joints.</p>
</li>
<li>Collagen Dream: Collagen-infused hot chocolate that guides you into a peaceful slumber, and awakens you with revitalised beauty.</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Is collagen safe for pregnant and nursing mothers?</strong></h3>
<p>Yes, our collagen is perfectly safe for both pregnant and nursing mothers. In fact, there are many benefits of taking collagen whilst pregnant. Many of our customers have already experienced the benefits with skin elasticity, minimising the appearance of stretch marks and getting a radiant glow. Additionally, it promotes strong and healthy hair, already helping our customers to combat postpartum hair loss.<br><br>For any specific concerns, we recommend consulting with your general practitioner, who can provide personalised advice tailored to your needs.</p>
<h3><strong>Can I take all the products together? Is there a limit?</strong></h3>
<p>There’s no official limit on collagen intake, so you can enjoy it your way! Our collagen products are made to complement each other, giving you the ultimate glow. If you’re just starting your collagen journey, you may want to start with 1 serving a day and gradually increase as you feel. It’s all about finding your glow-getting groove!</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>GUT</s:tag>
    <s:tag>how-to-greens</s:tag>
    <s:tag>icons-greens</s:tag>
    <s:tag>IMMUNITY</s:tag>
    <s:tag>OVERALL</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SKIN</s:tag>
    <s:tag>tiered</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/products/8111857205406</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="AUD">65.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SBG-AB28LP</s:sku>
      <s:grams>420</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/products/8111852781726</id>
    <published>2024-11-26T05:36:05+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-11-26T05:36:05+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.thecollagen.co/products/strawberry-kiwi-super-beauty-greens-308g"/>
    <title>Strawberry Kiwi Super Beauty Greens - 308g</title>
    <s:type></s:type>
    <s:vendor>The Collagen Co.</s:vendor>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<table border="0">
  <tr>
    <td width="200"><img width="200" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0423/1492/4190/files/strawberry-kiwi-super-beauty-greens-308g-324774.png?v=1732650972"></td>
    <td valign="bottom">
      <p>

        <strong>Vendor: </strong>The Collagen Co.<br>
        <strong>Type: </strong><br>
        <strong>Price: </strong>
            65.00
      </p>
    </td>
  </tr>
  <tr>
    <td colspan="2"><h2>Description</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><span>We've given the traditional (read: could-be-better) greens powder a massive upgrade. Formulated specifically for daily beauty, immune, digestion, and energy support, every serving of Strawberry Kiwi Super Beauty Greens packs a comprehensive functional, active stack of:</span></p>
<ul>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5,000mg Hydrolysed Collagen Peptides (Bovine)</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5 crucial, detoxifying Organic Greens</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>17 nutrient-dense Superfoods</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>Natural Sea Mineral Complex for a wealth of calcium and trace minerals</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>6 energising Herbal Extracts </li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>4 microbiome-nourishing Prebiotics</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5 gut-friendly Probiotics (5.6 billion CFUs)</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span>5 bloat-deterring Digestive Enzymes<span style="font-weight: 400;"></span>
</li>
</ul>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Naturally flavoured and sweetened with no added sugar for a spike-free wellness experience that'll have you feeling good down to the last sip.</span></p>
<h2>Benefits</h2>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Strawberry Kiwi Super Beauty Greens is a more-in-one wellness solution that does it all.</span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>It unites a blend of Organic Greens (such as Spirulina and Chlorella), antioxidant-rich Superfoods (from Blackcurrant to Elderberry to Broccoli Sprout), and Natural Sea Mineral Complex to support detoxification and immune health. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Hydrolysed Collagen Peptides effortlessly refine the complexion plus provide serious TLC to hair and nails. </span><b></b></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>What's more, Strawberry Kiwi Super Beauty Greens combines Pre and Probiotics and Digestive Enzymes to promote a balanced gut microbiome and support food breakdown, helping you extract the most nutrition from your diet while providing digestive comfort and alleviating the occasional bloating. </span></p>
<p dir="ltr"><span>Finally, a blend of herbal extracts, from L-theanine to Panax Ginseng, offers long-lasting energy that'll have you beating the afternoon slump and powering through your days — no matter how long they are.</span></p>
<h2>Ingredients</h2>
<ul></ul>
<ul class="ul1">
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Organic Greens Blend (Spirulina, Chlorella, Alfalfa Grass, Wheat Grass, Barley Grass)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>- Spirulina is a blue-green microalgae rich in protein, B vitamins, and antioxidants like phycocyanins.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Chlorella is a green algae that contains chlorophyll, which aids detoxification. It's also high in antioxidant compounds, such as carotenoids, like lutein, beta-carotene, and zeaxanthin.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Alfalfa Grass has a long history of use as a medicinal herb for humans. It's a good source of calcium, potassium, phosphorus, iron, and vitamins A, C, E, and K.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Wheat Grass is a great source of cleansing chlorophyll, vitamins and minerals (vitamins A, B, C, and E, iron, calcium, and magnesium), antioxidant compounds, and bioflavonoids, such as apigenin.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Barley Grass is rich in vitamins C, B, and minerals like calcium, iron, and magnesium.<br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<b>100% Hydrolysed Collagen Peptides (Bovine</b>)<br><span class="s1"></span>Hydrolysed bioactive collagen from grass-fed, pasture-raised bovine. A tailored blend that stimulates type 1, type 2, and type 3 collagen. Combined, these promote healthy hair, skin, and nails, improve joint function, and support gut health.<br><br>
</li>
<li class="li2">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Super Fruit Juice Blend (Blackcurrant, Raspberry, Strawberry, Pomegranate, Blueberry, Cranberry, Elderberry, Acai, Goji)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>These 5 super fruits offer a high concentration of vitamins, minerals, fibre, and antioxidants. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>Of particular importance for beauty and overall health is vitamin C, which may help protect against oxidative stress by scavenging destructive free radicals and stimulating the body's natural production of collagen, plus hyaluronic acid. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Organic Fruit and Vegetable Blend (Beetroot, Carrot, Kale, Spinach, Acai, Grape, Apple, Broccoli Sprout)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>Eight incredibly nutrient-dense fruits and vegetables with high amounts of essential vitamins, minerals, antioxidants, and fibre that you may be missing out on your daily diet. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>An unfamiliar ingredient that might have caught your eye is Broccoli Sprout — this refers to a 3-5 day-old broccoli seed sprout that offers more nutrition benefits than the mature plant, including increased concentrations of powerful antioxidants like vitamin C and a phytochemical called sulforaphane. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Natural Sea Mineral Complex<br></b><span class="s1"></span>Derived from red marine algae. A rich source of bioavailable calcium and 72 trace minerals, including magnesium, iron, and selenium, Natural Sea Mineral Complex offers a fuss-free way to fill the nutrition gaps in your diet. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Prebiotics (Partially Hydrolysed Guar Gum, Chicory Root Fibre, Acacia Fibre, Organic Green Banana Resistant Starch Powder)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>These 4 prebiotic fibres aren't digestible by your body, so they travel down to your lower digestive tract relatively intact and become a crucial food source for your gut's friendly microorganisms. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>This encourages a balanced gut microbiome, which promotes an optimal environment for your digestive system and overall health.<br><br>
</li>
<li class="li2">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Probiotics Blend (<i>Lactobacillus acidophilus, Lactobacillus plantarum, Lactobacillus rhamnosus, Bifidobacterium lactis, Bifidobacterium longum</i>)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>If prebiotics are "fertilisers" for beneficial gut microbes, probiotics are the "seeds" that'll populate your digestive tract and improve the composition of your gut microbiome. <br><br><span class="s1"></span>Different strains of probiotics perform different biological actions in the gut; the 5 probiotic strains in Super Beauty Greens were specifically selected for their unique and synergistic benefits in supporting overall health, vitality, gut, and immune support. <br><br>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<span class="s1"></span><b>Digestive Enzyme Blend (Protease, Amylase, Lipase, Cellulase, Lactase)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>A comprehensive blend of 5 digestive enzymes that support good digestion — promoting optimal nutrient absorption while minimising the occasional gas and bloating. <br><span class="s1"></span>- Protease enzymes break down proteins into smaller peptides and amino acids for absorption. <br>- Amylase enzymes break down carbohydrates into simpler sugars like glucose for absorption.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Lipase enzymes break down dietary fats into fatty acids and glycerol for absorption.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Cellulase enzymes break down cellulose, a plant fibre humans can't digest without assistance.<br><span class="s1"></span>- Lactase enzymes break down lactose, the sugar found in dairy products. <br><br><b></b>
</li>
<li class="li1">
<b>Herbal Extract Blend (L-theanine, Panax Ginseng, Cacao Bean Polyphenols, Milk Thistle, Gotu Kola)<br></b><span class="s1"></span>A blend of natural, energising actives that'll have you maintaining peak performance from day to night. Get ready to live your best life.</li>
</ul>
<h2>Nutritional Information</h2>
<p><img alt="" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0423/1492/4190/files/SBG_-_Strawberry_Kiwi_-_NIPS.png?v=1732526967" width="500" height="888"></p>
<h2>How to Use</h2>
<p>Fill your glass or bottle with 250-350ml of cold or hot water.</p>
<p>Add 1 serving (2 heaped scoops) to the water, and blend well.<b></b></p>
<p>One serving a day is recommended for the best results.<b></b></p>
<p>Store in a cool, dark place out of direct sunlight.</p>
<h2>Common FAQs</h2>
<h3><strong>Can Super Beauty Greens be taken alongside Glow shakes, Premium Collagen Peptides and/or Collagen Dream?</strong></h3>
<p>Absolutely, you can take Super Beauty Greens with Glow shakes and/or Premium Collagen Peptides! All of our collagen products are designed to complement each other.</p>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Super Beauty Greens: Boost your fruit and veggie game effortlessly, packed with collagen, Prebiotics, Probiotics, and Digestive Enzymes to keep you light, energised, and bloat-free.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Glow Shakes: These shakes are designed to help with weight management, skin health, and overall wellness with 29 grams of protein and collagen peptides.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>Premium Collagen Peptides: Added skin loving ingredients like hyaluronic acid and supports skin elasticity, hair, nails, and joints.</p>
</li>
<li>Collagen Dream: Collagen-infused hot chocolate that guides you into a peaceful slumber, and awakens you with revitalised beauty.</li>
</ul>
<h3><strong>Is collagen safe for pregnant and nursing mothers?</strong></h3>
<p>Yes, our collagen is perfectly safe for both pregnant and nursing mothers. In fact, there are many benefits of taking collagen whilst pregnant. Many of our customers have already experienced the benefits with skin elasticity, minimising the appearance of stretch marks and getting a radiant glow. Additionally, it promotes strong and healthy hair, already helping our customers to combat postpartum hair loss.<br><br>For any specific concerns, we recommend consulting with your general practitioner, who can provide personalised advice tailored to your needs.</p>
<h3><strong>Can I take all the products together? Is there a limit?</strong></h3>
<p>There’s no official limit on collagen intake, so you can enjoy it your way! Our collagen products are made to complement each other, giving you the ultimate glow. If you’re just starting your collagen journey, you may want to start with 1 serving a day and gradually increase as you feel. It’s all about finding your glow-getting groove!</p></td>
  </tr>
</table>
]]>
    </summary>
    <s:tag>GUT</s:tag>
    <s:tag>how-to-greens</s:tag>
    <s:tag>icons-greens</s:tag>
    <s:tag>IMMUNITY</s:tag>
    <s:tag>label:Best Seller</s:tag>
    <s:tag>OVERALL</s:tag>
    <s:tag>SKIN</s:tag>
    <s:tag>tiered</s:tag>
    <s:variant>
      <id>https://www.thecollagen.co/products/8111852781726</id>
      <title>Default Title</title>
      <s:price currency="AUD">65.00</s:price>
      <s:sku>SBG-SK28LP</s:sku>
      <s:grams>420</s:grams>
    </s:variant>
  </entry>
</feed>
